moviesmac.com 2013-04-30

# iSkysoft Privacy Policy

At iSkysoft, your security and privacy is the utmost importance to us. We will only collect your personal information for defined purposes. We do not distribute or share your personal information beyond what is strictly necessary to fulfill our obligations to you. We may share your information only with partners who adhere to iSkysoft's commitment to protect your privacy. iSkysoft Studio will not sell your personal information in any manner whatsoever.

As such, iSkysoft is committed to ensuring that its customers are informed as to how their personal information will be used and kept secure.

####  1\. What information do we collect?

iSkysoft may collect information from you relating to your identity and your personal preferences as they relate to our products. Personal information we may typically collect includes your name, address, email address, telephone number, IP address and in relation to purchases you may make, your credit card number. iSkysoft will endeavor only to collect such information as is necessary for the stated purpose for which iSkysoft is collecting the information. For example, if you purchase one iSkysoft product, we will require your name and address so that we can send the product to you and your credit card details to obtain payment. Our objective is to inform you before or at the time of collection as to the information we are collecting and the purposes for which we wish to use such information. If we require further information, we will identify the information we wish to collect and the purposes for which such information is being collected. If you choose not to provide required information, iSkysoft may not be able to comply with your request or provide certain services.

####  2\. How do we collect the information?

There are numbers of different ways that iSkysoft receives and collects personal information from you. Ways iSkysoft collects personal information from you may include the following:

**Communications from You**

When you email or write to us you may need to provide us your name, contact details, and other personal information in your message.

**Customer Support**

You may need to provide us personal information when you telephone or email us to request technical assistance in respect of our products or to request information that you would like to receive relating to our products.

**Email/Direct Mail Campaigns**

From time to time we may contact you directly by mail, email or telephone informing you about upgrades, new products, promotions or special offers that may be of interest to you. When responding to one of these campaigns, you may provide us with personal information.

**Registration of Products**

Upon registration of one iSkysoft product you will be asked to provide certain information which we will use to record you as an owner of the iSkysoft product and to assist us in providing you with service and information.

**Purchases**

If you wish to purchase iSkysoft products from our Store, we will require sufficient information to complete your purchase including your credit card details, your contact details and an address for shipping.

**Surveys**

From time to time we may conduct surveys in respect of our products and services. Participation in our surveys is optional. When you respond to one of our surveys, you may provide us with personal information about you.

####  3\. How do 3rd party credit card processors protect customer information?

iSkysoft software uses secure server hosted by SWREG and other 3rd party credit card processors that encrypt all the customer's personal information including name, address, credit card number credit card expiration date etc. before it is sent to us. Encryption works to prevent any malicious use of your personal information. Your credit card information is only used for online transition.

Credit card information in encrypted during the ordering process and is deleted as soon as your order is completed. All other personal information (name, address and product ordered) is held to assist product registration.

####  4\. SWREG?

SWREG is an advanced secure online payment service for software registration that has been in operation since 1987. iSkysoft Studio uses SWREG to provide you with very secure and fast online purchase.

####  5\. What are the purposes for iSkysoft uses the information?

iSkysoft may use your personal information for the following purposes:

**Product Registration**

Information you provide upon registration will be used to keep a record of your product and will assist iSkysoft in providing support to you when you contact iSkysoft's Customer Relationship Management System. iSkysoft will also use this information to inform you of any upgrades, new products, promotions or other information that may be of interest to you.

**Newsletters**

We may use your personal information to send you newsletters that provide you with articles and information that we believe may be of interest to you.

**Information in Respect of iSkysoft Products**

It is important for us to receive feedback from our customers in respect of our products and any features they would like to see in future products. As such, we may use your personal information to contact you about our products and to inform you of upgrades, promotions and new products that may be of interest to you.

**Internal Analysis**

We may use the information you provide us with for our own internal statistical and analytical purposes, to evaluate and profile customers including customer preferences and purchasing trends which we may use for marketing purposes and in respect of operations and development.

####  6\. About cookies?

In order to better understand what services are valuable to our customers, we use "cookies".

A cookie is a small text file that a website writes to your hard drive. Cookies work as your identification card and may record passwords, preferences and purchases. Cookies let the web page server know that you have returned to this site. Cookies also can determine other information, such as the daily visitors to our web site and the pages of the site most frequently visited. Cookies are unique and can only be read by the server that assigns them. They cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses.

You can change the settings in your browser to prevent cookies if you do not want to have a cookie set when you visit our website. However, by doing so, you may not have full access to all the web pages.

Check the End User License Agreement>>
